# **NGUYEN THI THUY VINH**

# **Employee Trainer**

**Mobile** : +84 3838 222 94

**Email**: thuyvinhnguyen1991@gmail.com

**Address**: 2/83 Pham Van Bach, Tan Binh, HCM City

**Date of Birth**: 15<sup>th</sup> April, 1991

Gender : Female

Marital Status : Single



### **CAREER OBJECTIVE**

Seeking a position that will utilize my potential, my educational background and knowledge of pharmaceuticals for developing of company. Looking to join a company that provides opportunity to apply my skills as a pharmacist.

Working hard to accumulate experience and knowledge, become a specialist in next 1 years of working.

### **EDUCATION**

Aug 2015 - Oct 2018	University of Medicine and Pharmacy, Ho Chi Minh City
	Bachelor of Pharmacy
Oct 2010 – Nov 2014	Score: 7.0  Industrial University, Ho Chi Minh City
	Bachelor of Biotechnology
	Score: 7.9

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

Jun 2018 – Aug 2018 Collaborators for Reli USA Company

Main responsibilities: seeking, translating, demonstrating the uses and mechanism of medicines, food supplements from the resources of NCBI, PUBMED, reputation science magazines, support the registration of medicines and food supplements. For

example: Coenzyme Q10, Omega 3, Collagen, Tocopherol, Vitamin B6, B2, K2,...

Knowledge of the regulations on marketing and advertisement for food supplements.

### **CERTIFICATIONS**

2018

TOEIC Certificate with score 600

### **SKILLS AND ABILITIES**

Computer	MS Word, MS Excel, MS Power Point, Photoshop, Corel.
Other	Good in reading and translating English medical document.
	Presentation skills, effective communication, have a pleasant
	tone of voice, scientific presentation and easy to understand for
	people.
	Good knowledge of the pharmaceutical, clinical medicine,
	physiological mechanisms, pathology, and related issues.
	Having a passion for training, teaching and sharing knowledge.
	Good ability to learn, understand, remember, analyze
	information and document management.
	Flexible, hard-working, cautious, team player and can work well
	in a high pressure environment.

### **INTERESTS**

Reading detective novel, listening music and traveling.

### **REFERENCES**

Mr. Tran Anh Hoang

RA Management in RELIUSA INC

Email: anhhoanghk92@gmail.com

Mobile: +84 975 6969 36

# NGUYỄN THỊ THỦY VINH

# Nhân Viên Huấn Luyện

**Điện thoại**: 03838 222 94

**Email**: thuyvinhnguyen1991@gmail.com

Địa chỉ : 2/83 Phạm Văn Bạch, Q.Tân Bình, TpHCM

**Ngày sinh**: 15/04/1991

Giới tính : Nữ

Tình trang: Đôc thân



# MỤC TIỀU NGHÈ NGHIỆP

Tìm kiếm công việc phù hợp với năng lực và nhu cầu của bản thân, tận dùng được tối đa kiến thức và kinh nghiệm trong lĩnh vực Y Dược vì sự phát triển của Công ty.

Làm việc thật tích cực để tích lũy kiến thức và kinh nghiệm, phát triển bản thân trở thành chuyên viên trong vòng 1 năm.

## **H**QC VÁN

08/2015 – 10/2018	Đại học Y Dược Thành phố Hồ Chí Minh
	Chuyên ngành: Dược sĩ Đại học
	Điểm: 7,0
10/2010 — 11/2014	Đại học Công Nghiệp Thành phố Hồ Chí Minh
	Chuyên ngành: Công nghệ Sinh học
	Điểm: 7,9

## KINH NGHIỆM LÀM VIỆC

06/2018 - 08/2018 Cộng tác viên cho công ty Reli USA.

Công việc chính: Tìm kiếm, dịch thuật và chứng minh công dụng, cách sử dụng, cơ chế tác động của thuốc, thực phẩm chức năng từ các nguồn tài liệu chuyên ngành như NCBI, PUBMED, và các tạp chí khoa học uy tín. Hỗ trợ cho việc đăng ký thuốc và thực phẩm chức năng. Các hoạt chất từng thực hiện qua như:

Coenzyme Q10, Omega 3, Collagen, Tocopherol, Vitamin B6, B2, K2,...

Nắm vững các quy định của Cục Quản Lý Dược, Cục Vệ Sinh An Toàn Thực Phẩm đối với việc thiết kế nhãn, quảng cáo thuốc và thực phẩm chức năng.

## CHÚNG CHỈ

2018 TOEIC 600
Tin học B

### KỸ NĂNG

Máy tính	MS Word, MS Excel, MS Power Point, Photoshop, Corel.
Khác	Kỹ năng đọc và dịch tiếng Anh chuyên ngành rất tốt.
	Kỹ năng thuyết trình, truyền đạt thông tin hiệu quả, trình bày
	khoa học dễ hiểu, giọng nói dễ gây thiện cảm, chú ý với người
	nghe.
	Kiến thức chuyên môn về sinh lý, bệnh học, cơ chế tác động của
	các hoạt chất và các vấn đề liên quan tốt.
	Vô cùng yêu thích công việc huấn luyện, chia sẻ kiến thức.
	Khả năng tiếp thu điều mới, ghi nhớ, phân tích thông tin và quản
	lý hồ sơ tài liệu.
	Chăm chỉ, cần thận, có kỹ năng làm việc nhóm và có thể làm việc
	dưới áp lực cao.

# SỞ THÍCH

Nghe nhạc, đọc tiểu thuyết trinh thám và du lịch.

## THAM KHẢO

Trần Anh Hoàng

Trưởng phòng Pháp lý – Công ty Cổ phần Reli USA

Email: anhhoanghk92@gmail.com

Điện thoại: 0975 6969 36